DAYS!
By the decision of Ying Zheng, the king that wished to unite all of China,
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
天下統一の道を行く王 嬴政(えいせい)のもと
the State of Qin began its invasion of the State of Wei.
秦国(しんこく)は 魏国(ぎこく)へと侵攻した
The enemy blocking their way is the legendary Great General, Lian Po.
立ちはだかる敵は
伝説の大将軍 廉頗(れんぱ)
若き将たちは 大いなる武功を狙い
この苛烈な戦場に挑む
Young generals take on this relentless battlefield in hopes of rendering great military achievements.
（桓騎(かんき)）
言い残すことはあるか？ じいさん
Any last words, Gramps?
You may be ignorant,
（玄峰(げんぽう)）ものを知らぬが
確かに筋は悪くない …か
but you certainly have talent, I suppose.
I wouldn't mind taking you on as a disciple, Huan Ji.
弟子にしてやってもよいぞ 桓騎
（斬る音）
要るかよ
Like I want your help,
small fry.
雑魚が
Forgive me, Xuan Feng.
（廉頗）許せ 玄峰…
つまらぬ死に方をさせた
I let you die a boring death...
I can't say anything too soft while I'm on the battlefield,
戦場で生ぬるいことは言えぬが
あれだけ共に
死線を越えてきた うぬを失うとは
but losing you after we faced death together so many times is...
But there's no reason to feel lonely, Xuan Feng.
だが 寂しがることはないぞ 玄峰
Soon that side will be flooded with the corpses of State of Qin soldiers!
すぐに 秦国兵の骸(むくろ)で
そっちをあふれ返してやるからな
We did it!
（兵士）やったぜ！
General Huan Ji's awesome!
（慶(けい)）桓騎将軍 すげえ！
（昂(こう)）おいらたち中央軍の敵(かたき)を
取ってくれたんだ
He got revenge for us, the central army!
All right!
（尾平(びへい)）良かった！
あのじじい また妙な術を
仕掛けてくるんじゃねえかって
Even I was afraid that old man would be coming at us with another weird strategy!
さすがの俺もビクついてたんだよ
（田永(でんえい)）
尾平のビビリは いつもじゃねえか
Wei Ping, you're always afraid!
（尾平）アハッ… アハハッ！
Xuan Feng...
（信(しん)）玄峰…
（信）信じられねえ　あのじじいが
あっさり やられるなんて
I can't believe it... That old man got done in that easily?
Are you sure, Meng Tian?
間違いねえのか？ 蒙恬(もうてん)
Yeah.
（蒙恬）ああ
桓騎将軍自ら伝令兵に変装して
Apparently General Huan Ji personally disguised himself as a messenger soldier and snuck into the enemy headquarters.
敵の本陣に忍び込んだらしい
（信）なに？ もっと詳しく教えろ
What?!
Could you be a little more detailed about it?
…と その前に
Well, before that,
I've got somewhere to go.
行く所があるんだ
お前も一緒に来い
Why don't you come with me?
えっ… 行く所？
Somewhere to go?
Meng Tian's Proposal
（武将）輪虎(りんこ)将軍
General Lun Hu, I understand how you feel, but we really must begin the war council.
お気持ちは分かりますが
軍議を開いてください
Due to the errors in the left army, everyone is clamoring about what strategy we should take as the central army.
左軍の失態により 我ら中央軍の
作戦は どうなるのかと―
皆が騒いでおります
Could you please—
どうか…
（輪虎）うるさいなぁ
Man, you're noisy.
I lost my parents in a war
（輪虎）僕は 戦で両親を失い
and I was saved by my lord when I was at the verge of starvation.
飢え死にしそうなところを
殿に助けられた
Since then, I've devoted everything to become my lord's sword,
それからの僕は―
殿の剣となるために
全てをささげたわけだけど
but it was actually Lord Xuan Feng that taught me strategy.
（輪虎）実際に戦術なんかを
教えてくれたのは 玄峰さまだった
It's always felt to me that my lord is my father and that man is my grandfather.
僕にとって
殿が父なら あの人は祖父
I had a great debt with the second of those two people.
２番目に
恩を返さなきゃいけない人だった
確かに 討たれたからには
ヘマをした玄峰さまが悪いんだけど
Of course, seeing as he was the one beaten,
Lord Xuan Feng is the one at fault,
but if you say something like "I understand how you feel" so casually
“気持ちは分かる”なんて
軽々しく言われると―
正直 イラッと来るな
I honestly get pretty annoyed.
E-Excuse me. I was just...
い… いえ… それは…
Don't worry about it.
（輪虎）心配いらない
After tonight, my lord will have cemented a whole new strategy.
今夜 ひと晩で
殿は新しい戦略を固められる
Then the only thing left will be to follow it.
僕らは それに従うだけだ
Yes, sir!
Why the hell did I hafta come to a place like this?!
なんで俺が こんなとこに
来なきゃなんねえんだよ？
そう言うなって
大事な話があるんだからさ
Hey, don't be like that. I've got something really important to tell you here.
And aren't you worried, seeing what bad shape the Yufeng Unit is in?
それに このところの玉鳳(ぎょくほう)隊の
調子の悪さを見ると 心配だろう？
Or about that guy's wound?
あいつのケガの具合も
ぜ… 全然！
I ain't friggin' worried!
お見舞いに来たよ 王賁(おうほん)　入るぞ
We're here to visit you on your sickbed, Wang Ben!
We're coming in now!
（信）アア…
（蒙恬）あら 元気そう
Ah, he looks pretty healthy.
What do you want?
（王賁）何の用だ？
（蒙恬）ハハッ…
Ya see! There's no point in worryin' about this guy!
ほらな！ こんなヤツ
心配するだけ損なんだよ
You're in the way. Get out.
ジャマだ　出ていけ
（信）言われなくたって出ていくぜ
You don't need to tell me twice!
Hey, now.
（蒙恬）まあまあ…
王賁も 信も 座って座って
C'mon, Wang Ben, Xin, sit down.
（信･王賁）お前が仕切るな！
Don't tell me what to do!
You've heard about how Xuan Feng was slain, Wang Ben?
（蒙恬）
桓騎将軍が玄峰を討ったこと
王賁も聞いたよね？
Yeah.
（王賁）ああ
（蒙恬）驚いたろう
Were you surprised?
Not really.
別に
（信）ウソつけ！
You liar!
ハハッ… お前たち２人が手も足も
出なかった玄峰を瞬殺だからな
Well you two couldn't lay a finger on that guy, and then he got killed instantly.
Shut up!
うるせえ！
If I'd aimed by spear just a little better, I would've taken that old man out!
俺の槍(やり)は もうちょっとで
あのじじいに届くとこだったんだ
フフフッ… 俺は驚いたよ
I'm surprised.
I'd heard that General Huan Ji was a military genius,
桓騎将軍は戦の天才だと
聞いていたが
but I honestly didn't think he'd be able to pull off something this big.
正直 ここまで大仕事を
やってのけるとは思っていなかった
So I'm saying that as people aiming for the top, we have some huge walls right in front of us.
上を目指す俺たちの すぐ上には
でっかい壁があるって話さ
Including how to overcome those walls, we need to think about what we're going to do from here.
その壁を越えるためにも―
これからのことを
考えておかないとな
This is the headquarters where the State of Qin Army Supreme Commander, General Meng Ao, is located.
これが 秦国軍の
総大将 蒙驁(もうごう)将軍がいる本陣
その前方に 俺たちの
組み込まれている中央軍が布陣し…
The army we're a part of, the central army, will be in formation just in front of there.
To our right will be the right army, led by General Huan Ji.
俺たちの右には
桓騎将軍率いる右軍
And on the left, the left army led by Wang Jian will be developing.
左には 王翦(おうせん)将軍率いる左軍が
展開している
On the other side of things, the State of Wei headquarters will be around here...
一方 敵 魏国軍の本陣は この辺り
ここに敵の総大将 白亀西と…
This is where the enemy Supreme Commander, Bai Guixi...
and most likely, Lian Po, will be.
恐らく 今のところは廉頗がいる
In front of the enemy headquarters will be the army directly in front of us, the enemy central army led by Lun Hu.
敵の本陣の前方
俺たちの正面に―
輪虎の率いる
敵の中央軍がいて…
And I would expect armies on the left and right will be developing.
やはり 右と左にも
軍が展開している
前置きが長いぞ
さっさと本題に入れ
That's enough of a preface.
Get to the point already.
フゥ…
（蒙恬）玄峰を討ったあと…
After slaying Xuan Feng,
General Huan Ji and his subordinates disappeared altogether.
桓騎将軍は
配下の兵もろとも姿を消した
一気に
敵の本陣を狙うのでは？
One could make the assumption they would head straight for the enemy headquarters, but...
…という推測もあるが
they actually drew back, rushing to regroup their army.
実は 後方に下がって
軍の立て直しを急いでる
立て直し？
Regroup?
Yes. Xuan Feng made light of Huan Ji,
ああ　玄峰は桓騎を侮ったが
桓騎も介子坊(かいしぼう)を侮った
but Huan Ji also made light of Jie Zifang.
General Huan Ji's headquarters was attacked by Jie Zifang's army
（蒙恬）桓騎将軍の本陣は
介子坊の軍の襲撃を受け―
兵士の半数を失ったそうだ
（信）介子坊？
and it seems he lost half of his soldiers.
Jie Zifang?
The general leading the enemy left army.
敵の左軍を率いている将軍だ
But having lost track of Huan Ji, Jie Zifang has to always be on his guard.
とはいえ 桓騎を見失った介子坊も
うかつには動けない
And on the opposite side of the battlefield,
一方 戦場の反対側では―
it seems that the one leading the enemy right army, Jiang Yan, has moved in to attack,
敵の右軍を率いる姜燕(きょうえん)が
攻め込んできたようだけど
but I don't see it as possible that General Wang Jian will simply be overcome by that.
王翦将軍が そのまま
押し切られるなんて ありえない
Don't you think, Wang Ben?
だろう？ 王賁
In other words, both the right army and left army are at a stalemate.
つまり
右の軍も左の軍も膠着(こうちゃく)状態で
しばらくは
戦況が動きそうもないってことだ
So it doesn't look like the state of battle will be changing for a bit.
右や左の話は
それくらいでいいだろう
Well that's fine for the left and right armies.
But the one we're fighting is Lun Hu, right in the middle.
俺たちが戦ってるのは
真ん中の輪虎だ
You really don't understand anything, do you?
何も分かってないな お前は
What?!
なに？
信の言葉は
半分 合ってて 半分 間違ってる
Well Xin, what you said was half right and half wrong.
It's true that our problem lies with Lun Hu in the center,
確かに 俺たちにとって問題なのは
中央の輪虎なんだけど
その輪虎の動きが
左右の軍の動きと―
but Lun Hu's movements will be connected with the movements of the left and right armies.
密接に関係してるんだ
（信）えっ？
In these three days
（王賁）
この３日間 中央の輪虎軍は―
the Lun Hu Army in the center has been waiting to decide whether to push into their opponents on the right or the left,
右か左の軍が
相手を押し込むのを待っていて
本気を出していない
so they haven't been serious.
The reason we didn't have major casualties on the second day
２日目以降 こちらに
大した被害が出ていないのは―
守備に徹しているせいもあるが
was because they were focusing on defense.
We'd be correct in thinking that Lun Hu, one of Lian Po's Four Heavenly Kings, was not acting in all seriousness then.
廉頗四天王のひとり 輪虎が 本気を
出していないと考えるほうが妥当だ
Hey, did you do some investigating on Lun Hu, Wang Ben?
ひょっとして
輪虎のこと調べた？ 王賁
多少　部下に敵の捕虜を当たらせた
（蒙恬）なるほど… さすがだね
A little. I had my subordinates get it from enemy prisoners.
I see. Good thinking.
（信）ちょ… ちょっと待て！
ズルイぞ お前ら　俺にも教えろ！
H-Hold on a second!
That ain't fair, you guys!
Tell me this stuff, too!
廉頗の下には
四天王と呼ばれる４人の将軍がいる
Lian Po has four generals under him called the Four Heavenly Kings.
They're all genuinely strong people that have built up military experience fighting with Lian Po.
いずれも
廉頗と共に戦歴を重ねてきた―
極めつきの つわものたちだ
The head of the Four Heavenly Kings, Jie Zifang,
（蒙恬）四天王筆頭の介子坊は
廉頗と関わりなく―
is a military hero that has had victory in over 100 wars even without Lian Po.
単独でも 100を超える戦で
勝利を収めてきた豪傑
The expert bowman and one of China's Ten Bows, Jiang Yan,
中華十弓のひとりに
数えられる弓の名手 姜燕は―
かつて
趙国(ちょうこく)と対立していた国の英雄だ
was once a hero of a kingdom that once opposed the State of Zhao.
さんざん
廉頗を手こずらせたというが
They apparently caused a lot of trouble for Lian Po,
国が滅んだあとは
廉頗に忠誠を誓っている
but after their kingdoms crumbled, they swore loyalty to him.
Xuan Feng, a long-time officer under Lian Po,
（蒙恬）
長年 廉頗の参謀を務めた玄峰は
趙国軍全体の総司令を
任されるほどの実力を―
apparently was skilled enough to command the entire State of Zhao Army.
持っていたらしい
That old man... He was that good?
あのじじい そんなに偉かったのか
By the way, Xuan Feng also taught Lian Po war strategy in his younger days.
ちなみに 玄峰は 若き日の廉頗に
戦略を教えた師でもあった
その玄峰を弔うためにも…
And it's likely that as a way of mourning Xuan Feng,
Lian Po will do everything he can to win this war.
廉頗は全力で
この戦を勝ちに来るだろうな
And the last one, the one we're opposing now, Lun Hu.
そして 最後のひとり…
今 俺たちが
相手にしている輪虎だが
廉頗の戦歴を詳しく知ったら
分かった
From all I learned from Lian Po's war history, this is what became apparent,
the most dangerous one among the Four Heavenly Kings is indeed Lun Hu.
（蒙恬）やはり 四天王の中で
最も危険なのは この輪虎だ
廉頗が関わった大きな戦では―
In all of the big wars Lian Po was involved in,
必ず この男が
決定的な戦果を挙げている
that man always made decisive military gains.
とにかく
恐ろしい突破力を持っていて
He also boasts incredible ability to break through opposition.
輪虎に本陣を襲われた軍は
数知れない
Lun Hu has attacked countless enemy headquarters.
He's even penetrated General Wang Qi's headquarters
あの王騎(おうき)将軍も 本陣に突入され
輪虎に ひと太刀浴びせられている
（信）なに？
and struck a blow on him.
What?
He struck a blow... on Wang Qi?!
あの王騎将軍に…
ひと太刀 浴びせた？
I see...
なるほど…
So that Lun Hu hasn't shown his true colors yet.
まだ本気出してねえな 輪虎は
（蒙恬）全然ね
Not in the least.
If the enemy left army or right army gets behind General Meng Ao, blocking his escape route,
（王賁）敵の右軍か左軍が―
蒙驁将軍の後ろに回り
逃げ道を塞げば―
Lun Hu could push in for an attack on a moment's notice.
輪虎は
すかさず攻め込んでくるだろう
Do you think that we, the central army, could stop Lun Hu when he's attacking seriously?
本気で攻めてくる輪虎を―
俺たち中央軍で
止められると思うかい？
（王賁）はっきり言って ムリだな
（信）なっ…
Honestly, I don't.
やっぱ そうだよね
（信）ちょっと待て！
Yeah, you're probably right.
Hold on a second!
What're you guys talking about?!
何言ってんだ お前ら！
戦う前から諦めてんじゃねえ！
We can't give up before we've even fought!
桓騎が玄峰を討ったんなら―
Huan Ji took down Xuan Feng, so how can we say we're aiming even higher
その上を目指す俺たちが
輪虎を討たなくて どうするんだ？
if we can't take out Lun Hu?
This is the guy that struck a blow on General Wang Qi! I say, great!
（信）
王騎将軍に ひと太刀浴びせた輪虎
上等じゃねえか！
来るなら来いってんだ！
返り討ちにしてやる！
Let him come at us if he wants, we'll hit him right back!
All right, fine.
ケッ… ちょうどいい
I'm the one who first formed a connection to that guy, and my goal is the head of one general!
あいつと
最初に因縁ができたのは俺だし
目的の“将軍の首１つ”だ
I'll take the head of one of Lian Po's Four Heavenly Kings with my own hands!
廉頗四天王のひとり 輪虎の首は
必ず俺が この手で取ってやる
And then I'll move ahead of you two in one fell swoop!
そして 一気に
お前らの上に行ってやっからな！
ほえるだけなら誰でもできる
身の程知らずが
Anyone can talk big.
You idiot, you don't know your place.
What?!
Xin, you're half right, half wrong again.
信… 今度も
半分 合ってて 半分 間違い
じいさまの本陣を狙っている輪虎は
確かに討ち取らなくっちゃならない
It's true that since Lun Hu is targeting Grandfather's headquarters, we need to take him down.
だが 攻め込んでくるのを
返り討ちにするんじゃない
But we can't do that by countering when he attacks us.
Meng Tian, what exactly are you trying to say?
蒙恬… 貴様 何が言いたい？
攻めてくる輪虎を
止めるのがムリなら―
If stopping Lun Hu once he starts his attack is impossible,
then we just don't let him attack.
攻めさせなきゃいい
In other words, we wage an attack and defeat Lun Hu before he has a chance to attack.
つまり 輪虎が攻めてくる前に
こちらから仕掛けて 倒すのさ
Tomorrow, we have the Yuehua Unit, the Yufeng Unit, and the Feixin Unit attack in a group
明日 楽華(がくか)隊 玉鳳隊 飛信(ひしん)隊の
３隊で打って出て
and take down Lun Hu!
輪虎を討ち取ろう
Meng Tian
楽華隊！
Yuehua Unit!
この隊の長所は
緻密で冷静な戦い方と―
This unit's forte is that we can perform in a meticulous and level-headed fighting style,
泥くさい血みどろの戦い方
両方ができることだ
as well as an unrefined, bloody fighting style.
The young master is giving a pep-talk?
（じい）若が 檄(げき)を…
That's rare...
（陸仙(りくせん)）珍しいな
And today, we will be doing the latter.
（蒙恬）そして 今日は後者だ
As you know, I'm really not a fan of this sort of thing,
知ってのとおり
こういうノリは好きじゃないが
but right now there's something before us that only we can do.
俺たちにしかできないことが
今 目の前にある
Today's going to be a brutal life-or-death struggle!
今日は ひどい死闘になるぞ
I see. So that's what's going on?
なるほど… そういうことでしたか
He's intending to do an important job for the first time in a while.
久々に
重要な役目を果たすおつもりですな
悪いが よろしく頼むよ みんな
Sorry, but I'm really gonna be counting on you guys for this one.
What?
（番陽(ばんよう)）何だ？ 楽華隊の連中が
やけに張り切っているが
Those Yuehua guys sound really spirited about something.
The Yuehue Unit seems to be in a different mood than usual.
（楚水(そすい)）楽華隊の様子が
いつもと違いますな
Chu Shui.
楚水
（楚水）はっ！
I've got something I need to talk to you about.
（信）ちょっと話がある
General Lun Hu!
（伝令）輪虎将軍！
A message from the main headquarters!
（伝令）総本陣より 伝令です！
The battle will flow to the end of today.
“戦いは今日まで流す”
So the battle for avenging Lord Xuan Feng will start tomorrow?
玄峰さまの弔い合戦は明日以降か
Okay, how 'bout we get going then?
よし！ それじゃ 始めようか
（土門(どもん)）うろたえるな！
守備に徹すれば 問題はない！
Do not panic!
As long as you focus on defense, there will be no problems!
Keep your heads level and fight!
（土門）落ち着いて戦え！
（兵士たち）オーッ！
General Tu Men! We have a situation!
（部下）土門将軍 大変です！
命令を無視して
突撃していく部隊があります！
There is a unit that is ignoring orders and charging!
（土門）なに！
What?!
The Yuehua Unit?!
楽華隊か！
General Tu Men!
（伝令）土門将軍！
楽華隊の蒙恬千人将より伝達です
I have a message from Thousand-Man General Meng Tian of the Yuehua Unit!
The Yuehua Unit will now be acting as an independent army
“楽華隊は
これより独立軍となり―”
“兵200を残して
持ち場を離れる”とのことです
and will be leaving their post, leaving 200 soldiers behind!
なんだと！
What did you say?!
They've made killing them easier by saving us a trip!
（魏兵）わざわざ
討たれに出てくるとは手間が省ける
取り囲んで しとめろ！
（魏兵たち）オーッ！
Surround them and attack!
Yuehua Unit, progress to the right!
楽華隊！ 右に進め！
So that's Lun Hu's headquarters?
あれが輪虎の本陣
Lord Lun Hu, there is one enemy unit that is charging straight for us!
（圭）輪虎さま 敵軍の中に―
まっすぐ こちらに
突っ込んでくる部隊があります
Oh? I wonder if it's me they're aiming for?
ワハッ…
狙いは ここにいる僕かな？
秦国軍の作戦ではなさそうだけど
単独だとしたら…
That doesn't sound like a strategy the State of Qin Army would use,
so if someone's acting on their own...
まるで自殺行為だよ
That's pretty much suicide.
I know.
（蒙恬）分かってるよ
After we've been competing with each other all this time,
（蒙恬）これまで何かと
張り合ってきた俺たち３人が―
手を組むのが難しいことぐらい
I know the three of us teaming up will be pretty difficult.
But unless we try, we'll just all go down together.
でも このままじゃ 共倒れだ
As we are now, the Yuehua Unit can't beat Lun Hu alone.
今の楽華隊じゃ
単独で輪虎を討つことはできない
それは玉鳳隊も飛信隊も同じだ
The same goes for the Yufeng Unit and Feixin Unit.
Hey, don't go grouping the Feixin Unit in with that!
勝手に飛信隊を一緒にすんな
Although you've gotten by through being stubborn like this up till now,
今までなら こうやって 意地を
張り合っていても良かったけど
the situation has majorly changed.
状況が大きく変わってきた
（信）うん？
ここに至るまで ３つの城を落とし
Until we got here, we took down three castles
玉鳳隊 楽華隊 飛信隊と
それぞれ武功を上げてきたが
and the Yufeng Unit, Yuehua Unit, and Feixin Unit rendered our own individual achievements,
but to be perfectly honest, those achievements didn't even resonate within the State of Qin, let alone other kingdoms.
（蒙恬）
はっきり言って そんな武功など
ほかの国はおろか
秦国の国内にすら鳴り響いていない
だが…
But now, we're fighting the Lian Po.
俺たちは今 あの廉頗と戦っている
伝説の大将軍 廉頗が
参戦してきたことで―
Since the legendary Great General, Lian Po, is part of this war,
この山陽(さんよう)攻略の最終戦は―
all of China will have its eyes on this final battle for the capture of Shanyang.
中華全土が注目するものに
なったんだ
ハッ… 中華全土が注目…
All of China?
But as things stand, we cannot defeat Lun Hu.
（蒙恬）だが 今のままでは
輪虎を討つことはできない
輪虎を討てなければ―
And unless we do, our Supreme Commander, General Meng Ao, will be in danger.
こちらの総大将 蒙驁将軍の
首が危ない
もし蒙驁将軍が
討たれるようなことがあれば
If something like General Meng Ao being killed happens,
it won't be like the State of Zhao Army where they were trained and led by their own,
自らの手で鍛え上げ
自在に操れる趙国軍ではなく
よそ者として指揮をする魏国軍を
率いた廉頗に―
we would be defeated by the State of Wei Army led by Lian Po, and outside.
俺たちは敗れたことになる
Then how the hell could we ever call ourselves the greatest generals under the heavens?
“天下の大将軍”などと
どの口がたたく？
I didn't expect to hear the words "greatest generals under the heavens" from you, Meng Tian.
お前の口から“天下の大将軍”と
いう言葉が出るとはな 蒙恬
Yeah, I guess.
フッ… そうだな
On that note,
その辺に関しては―
俺は お前たちほど
熱いものは抱えちゃいない
I'm not as enthused about that as you two are.
But for this time, I'm a bit different
than I usually am, Wang Ben.
だが 今回ばかりは
いつもの俺とは違うんだよ 王賁
うん？
（蒙恬）さっきも言ったが―
I said this earlier,
but we can't let them take Meng Ao's head.
蒙驁の首を
取られるわけにはいかない
Because he's my dear Grandfather that's always looking after this wandering, carefree grandson of his.
フラフラ遊び回っている
俺みたいな孫を―
いつも見守ってくれている―
俺の大切なじいさまだからな
フッ… 自分１人の感情を
戦場に持ち込むなど…
You're bringing personal feelings onto the battlefield? Ridiculous...
くだらん
（信）くだらなくはねえ
It ain't ridiculous!
Everybody fights for the things that are important to them.
誰だって 自分の大事なもんや―
For the things they can't let go of!
譲れねえもんを守るために
戦ってるんだ
Okay, Meng Tian.
（信）いいぜ 蒙恬
飛信隊は お前に乗っかってやる
The Feixin Unit is on board with your plan.
It's about time we took the leading role in a war
そろそろ戦の主役が変わるって―
中華全土に
教えてやらねえといけねえしな
and told all of China who we were!
So, what're you gonna do, Wang Ben?
…で お前は どうする？ 王賁
It depends on your strategy.
作戦しだいだ
Okay, then I'll tell it to you.
（蒙恬）じゃ 作戦を言おう
First, the Yuehua Unit will target Lun Hu's headquarters on our own.
まずは
楽華隊が単独で輪虎の本陣を目指す
なるほど　錐行(すいこう)の陣か
I see.
A pyramid formation, eh?
その数で僕を狙うなら
一点突破しかないからねえ
If they're going for me with those numbers, their only chance is breaking through at one point.
Let's see it then, the State of Qin Army's penetrative power!
見せてもらおうか　秦国軍の突破力
Hold on a second. Then that means you're just going to take down Lun Hu yourself, doesn't it?!
（信）ちょっと待て！
それじゃ 結局 お前らだけで
輪虎を倒しに行くんじゃねえか
（蒙恬）
ハハッ… それができないから
策を講じてるんだろう
We're working out this plan because I can't do that, aren't we?
Here we go, everyone!
やるぞ みんな！
They're trying to break through at one point! Defensive unit, take your positions!
一点突破 来るぞ！ 守備隊 構え！
Now!
今だ！
What?!
なに？
For the first stage of the plan...
（蒙恬）作戦の第１段階
楽華隊は輪虎を狙わない
the Yuehua Unit will not target Lun Hu.
Preview
United Front
of Three Units
End